<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-02-01T06:56:49-08:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Casey Becking</title><subtitle></subtitle><entry><title type="html">Automations in Cyber Security</title><link href="/security/automation/2023/03/05/automation-in-cyber-security.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Automations in Cyber Security" /><published>2023-03-05T19:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2023-03-05T19:00:00-08:00</updated><id>/security/automation/2023/03/05/automation-in-cyber-security</id><content type="html" xml:base="/security/automation/2023/03/05/automation-in-cyber-security.html">&lt;p&gt;In today’s digital world, cyber threats are growing at an alarming rate. As organizations continue to adopt digital technologies, the risk of cyber attacks is becoming more prevalent. Cybersecurity experts have been constantly seeking solutions to improve the security posture of organizations. Automation in cybersecurity has emerged as one of the most effective solutions to address this challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Automation is the process of automating routine tasks and processes using software and technology. In the context of cybersecurity, automation refers to the use of technology to automatically detect, prevent, and respond to cyber threats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the key reasons why automation in cybersecurity is so important:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rapid threat detection and response – Cybersecurity automation allows organizations to detect and respond to cyber threats in real-time. Automated threat detection systems can analyze large volumes of data from different sources, such as logs, network traffic, and endpoints, to identify and prioritize potential threats. Once a threat is detected, automated response systems can take action to prevent the threat from causing damage.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Improved accuracy and consistency – Manual processes are prone to errors, inconsistencies, and delays. Cybersecurity automation can help organizations achieve greater accuracy and consistency in their security operations. Automated systems can perform tasks faster and more reliably than humans, reducing the risk of errors and ensuring that security policies are consistently applied.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Increased efficiency and scalability – Cybersecurity automation can also improve the efficiency and scalability of security operations. Automated systems can handle a large volume of security alerts and incidents, enabling security teams to focus on high-priority issues. Automation also reduces the need for manual intervention, freeing up staff to work on more strategic tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cost savings – Manual security operations are often time-consuming and labor-intensive, which can lead to higher costs. Automation can help organizations reduce the cost of security operations by minimizing the need for manual intervention and improving the efficiency of security operations.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Regulatory compliance – Many organizations are subject to regulatory compliance requirements, such as the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS). Cybersecurity automation can help organizations comply with these requirements by providing automated controls and processes that can be audited and documented.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, automation in cybersecurity is essential for organizations to effectively protect against cyber threats. Automation can help organizations detect and respond to threats faster, improve the accuracy and consistency of security operations, increase efficiency and scalability, reduce costs, and achieve regulatory compliance. As the threat landscape continues to evolve, cybersecurity automation will become even more critical for organizations to maintain a strong security posture.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="security" /><category term="automation" /><summary type="html">In today’s digital world, cyber threats are growing at an alarming rate. As organizations continue to adopt digital technologies, the risk of cyber attacks is becoming more prevalent. Cybersecurity experts have been constantly seeking solutions to improve the security posture of organizations. Automation in cybersecurity has emerged as one of the most effective solutions to address this challenge.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Security and ChatGPT</title><link href="/security/chatgpt/2023/03/05/security-and-chatgpt.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Security and ChatGPT" /><published>2023-03-05T18:40:00-08:00</published><updated>2023-03-05T18:40:00-08:00</updated><id>/security/chatgpt/2023/03/05/security-and-chatgpt</id><content type="html" xml:base="/security/chatgpt/2023/03/05/security-and-chatgpt.html">&lt;p&gt;Chatbots are quickly becoming an integral part of our lives, from customer service to healthcare. However, as with any technology, chatbots come with their own unique set of security risks. This blog post will discuss the security risks associated with chat GPT (general purpose text) and how organizations can protect themselves from these risks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chat GPT is a type of artificial intelligence (AI) system that can understand and respond to natural language input. It is used in a variety of applications, including customer service, healthcare, and education. While chat GPT can provide a more efficient and cost-effective way of interacting with customers, it also introduces a number of security risks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, chat GPT systems are vulnerable to malicious actors who can use the system to gain access to sensitive data. For example, an attacker could use a chatbot to impersonate a customer and gain access to confidential information. Additionally, malicious actors can use chatbots to launch phishing attacks and spread malware.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, chat GPT systems are vulnerable to data breaches. If a chatbot is not properly secured, an attacker could gain access to the system and steal or modify data. As a result, organizations must ensure that their chat GPT systems are properly secured with encryption and authentication protocols.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, chat GPT systems can be used to spread misinformation. For example, an attacker could use a chatbot to spread false information or manipulate public opinion. Organizations must be aware of this risk and take steps to ensure that their chatbot is not used for malicious purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Organizations can protect themselves from the security risks associated with chat GPT by following best practices such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Implementing strong authentication and encryption protocols&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Regularly monitoring the system for suspicious activity&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Ensuring that all data is securely stored and backed up&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Conducting regular security audits&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Implementing access control measures&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Training employees on security best practices&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By taking these steps, organizations can ensure that their chat GPT systems are secure and protected from malicious actors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Links to where you can find more information on this –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.accenture.com/us-en/insights/artificial-intelligence/chatbot-security-risks&quot;&gt;Accenture&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.csoonline.com/article/3300386/chatbot-security-risks-and-how-to-protect-against-them.html&quot;&gt;CSO Online&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="security" /><category term="chatgpt" /><summary type="html">Chatbots are quickly becoming an integral part of our lives, from customer service to healthcare. However, as with any technology, chatbots come with their own unique set of security risks. This blog post will discuss the security risks associated with chat GPT (general purpose text) and how organizations can protect themselves from these risks.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Make it your day job to find a job</title><link href="/employment/interviews/2019/03/11/make-it-your-day-job.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Make it your day job to find a job" /><published>2019-03-11T18:46:57-07:00</published><updated>2019-03-11T18:46:57-07:00</updated><id>/employment/interviews/2019/03/11/make-it-your-day-job</id><content type="html" xml:base="/employment/interviews/2019/03/11/make-it-your-day-job.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;make-it-your-day-job-to-find-a-job&quot;&gt;Make it your day job to find a job&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So right now I find my self looking for a new full time employment opportunity. I wanted to take some time to jot down how I’m doing this and how I think people should handle the opportunity that is present ed to them of being unemployed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a very early morning person I wake between 3-4am almost daily (weekends closer to 5) I go to the gym to get out of the house and go do something right when I wake up. I come back and setup some breakfast and get to planning my day. This gives me time to be able to eat and think before getting into my tasks and trust me I have a ton even while being unemployed. I go through my day just like I have a job but only now my job is to find a job, below will be a few things I like to be doing myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;stay-organized&quot;&gt;Stay organized&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Theres nothing like picking up the phone to talk to a potential future employer and not remembering their name. I save all of my information to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.evernote.com&quot;&gt;Evernote&lt;/a&gt; and break it down by the&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Company Name - Job Title - Persons Name(Role)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So in this case it would look something like this for a title&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Apple Inc - Senior DevOps Engineer - Julie(HR)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I take a ton of notes, this has allowed me to be be able to look back and ask questions based on conversations days ago. I still don’t have the best way to take notes but I know the more I do it the better I will get!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;be-patient&quot;&gt;Be patient&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t going to happen overnight, it will take time and rejection. Do not get bothered if an employers says you are not a good fit. I have to tell you, you wont be a good fit for everything and to be honest for most jobs you wont be. Take a quick walk away and plan the next interaction do not get bothered by rejection, get used to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;be-honest&quot;&gt;Be honest&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be honest with the person you are having a conversation with. If you don’t feel you want the position let them know. On the flip side of that if you really want this position be sure to work hard at that letting them know this is the position for you and you are going to pursue it as hard as possible. Also be able to say - that drive is a bit too far or that company isn’t aligned with my views, companies what you to be honest so they don’t have their time wasted either.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="employment" /><category term="interviews" /><summary type="html">Make it your day job to find a job</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Where has Casey Been</title><link href="/personal/2019/03/06/what-have-i-been-doing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Where has Casey Been" /><published>2019-03-06T17:46:57-08:00</published><updated>2019-03-06T17:46:57-08:00</updated><id>/personal/2019/03/06/what-have-i-been-doing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/personal/2019/03/06/what-have-i-been-doing.html">&lt;p&gt;What have I been doing in the past 2 years since my last post. &lt;strong&gt;A TON!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;professional&quot;&gt;Professional&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;build-engineer&quot;&gt;Build Engineer&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I became a build engineer in early 2017. As a build engineer the basic outline of the job is to take Design Documents and build out infrastructure. This could have been done via a command line interface or via an automation tool &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.terraform.io&quot;&gt;Terraform&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/cloudformation/aws-cloudformation-templates/&quot;&gt;Cloudformation&lt;/a&gt; templates). We spent time discussing with the customer their needs and wants as well as current architecture. Another team member would build out and diagram out for them what the environment would look like, we would take that visualization and make it into infrastructure. Once that infrastructure was standing up we would actually have to walk the customer through how to use this new infrastructure that we built for them. This is a long ongoing process of communication to external customers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;devops-engineer&quot;&gt;DevOps Engineer&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In late 2018 I became a DevOps Engineer on the Public Clouds team. We built tools and technology for internally and external teams to be able to do their job in a faster clip. This sometimes meant developing a set of tools for a customer to use to be able to build out infrastructure faster. We used all kinds of tools - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.terraform.io&quot;&gt;Terraform&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.packer.io&quot;&gt;Packer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.python.org/&quot;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gnu.org/software/bash/&quot;&gt;bash&lt;/a&gt;. We also had many opportunities to interface with customers MP that subject matter expert that they would reach out to regarding application infrastructure as well as the best architecture for them. This was always challenging but fun to be able to take on new projects every single day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;personal&quot;&gt;Personal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal and more recently I have been playing more Hockey. I have been spending as much time as possible with our daughter and getting to work remotely has helped that out immensely. I have been working on my health and fitness more by going to the gym 3-5 times a week and playing Hockey 2 times a week. I have also been meal prepping and eating better as often as possibly. No I’m not on a diet but I am eating better. I still do enjoy a little del taco or taco bell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s all that I can think of for right now but I will be updating this as often as possible will also be sharing more about my day-to-day and what I do with customers and clients.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="personal" /><summary type="html">What have I been doing in the past 2 years since my last post. A TON!!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I went to Futurestack 2016</title><link href="/rackspace/2017/01/03/future-stack-2016.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I went to Futurestack 2016" /><published>2017-01-03T17:46:57-08:00</published><updated>2017-01-03T17:46:57-08:00</updated><id>/rackspace/2017/01/03/future-stack-2016</id><content type="html" xml:base="/rackspace/2017/01/03/future-stack-2016.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why did I goto FutureStack 2016?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rackspace.com&quot;&gt;Rackspace&lt;/a&gt; prides itself on having the most educated engineers in the industry and being able to send specific engineers to conferences is a large value add for Rackspace as a whole. This is why I was able to attend the new relic future stack 2016 conference in San Francisco. Today I’m going to go over a few of the key takeaways from the conference and how they will be able to be used immediately within our clients infrastructure and application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What did I enjoy the most?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably the most exciting thing to come out of future stack this year’s new relics application named Infrastructure. Infrastructure allows you to be able to have complete visibility of you’re constantly changing architecture. With real-time metrics and a complete correlation of configuration changes you will be able to quickly resolve issues, scale rapidly, and deploy intelligently. We have already been using this with some of our beta clients and are already seeing the benefits of being able to see where configuration changes have been made and visualize the direct correlation to a spike in Page load time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another key feature of new relics infrastructure is the integrations that they have pre-built for Amazon web services. This has allowed us to be able to see a higher level of view of all the Amazon web services that are running on our clients infrastructure. We are now able to write new relic query (NRQL) language queries against this information and expose it in a beautiful dashboard for our clients to be able to see. They also have built-in support for many more integrations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With new relic infrastructure you are able to track health metrics and configuration changes in real time. What this allows you to do is be able to alert on key metrics four either infrastructure changes and/or health metrics. We have already been using this for our clients to be alerted when a scaling action happens within Amazon web services. We are now able to no women infrastructure is scaling up or scaling down through a simple alerting feature built into new relic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ability to filter new relics infrastructure based upon specific tags, instance types, display names or regions allows us to dive in a bit deeper into the details of your Amazon Web services infrastructure.  Four instance we will be able to see what inventory has been changed in what region and during what time this is a valuable data we will need to be able to properly triage a slowness in page load times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another new release that came out of the show was the ability to have a dynamic baselining alerts. Having the ability to be able to be platform/infrastructure agnostic and not care whether it’s a bare metal system that lives for years or a virtual machine that last for months or even a container that may live for only a few minutes we are now able to take recent data, trends and seasonality and weight all three behaviors, using them in combination to be able to better predict future changes. The benefits of new relic baseline alerts are the ability to be confident in the thresholds that are set based upon history, Minute scale granularity &amp;amp; sophisticated calculations as well as fast alert configurations via the NewRelic portal or API.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In closing today’s infrastructure is very different than what it was a few years ago the old tools of the trade are not sufficient to be able to keep up with the pace at which our technologies are ever-changing. We need tools as well as expertise to stay up-to-date with the new world coming. Servers are no longer living for long life spans and with a new relic infrastructure and new relic dynamic baselining alerts we are able to do this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please feel free to reach out Rackspace for more information on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rackspace.com/en-us/digital/managed-application-services/critical-applications&quot;&gt;Managed Application Support (MAS)&lt;/a&gt; or NewRelic for &lt;a href=&quot;https://newrelic.com/infrastructure&quot;&gt;NewRelic Infrastructre&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="rackspace" /><summary type="html">Why did I goto FutureStack 2016?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Killing the tech interview</title><link href="/interview/technical/2017/01/01/killing-the-tech-interview.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Killing the tech interview" /><published>2017-01-01T17:46:57-08:00</published><updated>2017-01-01T17:46:57-08:00</updated><id>/interview/technical/2017/01/01/killing-the-tech-interview</id><content type="html" xml:base="/interview/technical/2017/01/01/killing-the-tech-interview.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be Prepared&lt;/strong&gt; - Be sure to bring not only your resume but any additional things that you think you will need for the interview. Bring a notebook with a pen to be able to write down notes as well during the meeting it shows that you’re paying attention and if anything comes up it is always nice to be able to write it down as a note to go back later and research it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be early&lt;/strong&gt; - This is a major thing for me if you are not early you are late make sure you are early enough to where you can find the location park get to the building get inside and get settled be sure to sit down and relax I cannot stress enough being late to an interview will almost always be a negative factor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do your research&lt;/strong&gt; - These may not be in the particular order in which they will come actually but always prepare for the interview. Ask to know who you are going to be speaking to if it’s a round robin type of interview try to get the information out of the HR team to see if you can do some the Basic research on who you will be talking to. Try to find them on social media and take some notes on what key interests they have maybe they went to a specific school maybe they enjoyed a specific sport. Once you have a little bit of information use that inside of your interview during the conversation that people want to know that you are a real person and not just a robot here to take questions and spit back textbook answers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stay calm&lt;/strong&gt; - Try to stay as calm as possible the more interviews you do the easier they will become. I personally am just like to do interviews to do them to be able to have regular conversations and see what type of the questions  will be asked in the interview process. You will not win them all and some will lend a lot shorter than you would like just realize this is going to happen and hopefully it’s not going to happen on every single one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appreciate  the other persons Time&lt;/strong&gt; - Once the interview is starting to conclude be sure to think the other person for their time. They’re giving you an opportunity to be able to prove to them that you are a correct fit for this business. This is something that takes time out of their day and just show that you are appreciative of their time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow Up&lt;/strong&gt; - Give it a day or two before following up. I always start the email or follow up call with a question to make sure that they have all the information they need from me from be able to possibly fill the position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Extra&lt;/strong&gt; - Add the HR person and anybody who interviewed you on to your Social Media account (linkedin) this will also refresh their memory even if they do ignore you it’s okay.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="interview" /><category term="technical" /><summary type="html">Be Prepared - Be sure to bring not only your resume but any additional things that you think you will need for the interview. Bring a notebook with a pen to be able to write down notes as well during the meeting it shows that you’re paying attention and if anything comes up it is always nice to be able to write it down as a note to go back later and research it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hugo to Rackspace using TraviCIs</title><link href="/rackspace/hugo/development/2016/09/09/hugo-to-rackspace.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hugo to Rackspace using TraviCIs" /><published>2016-09-09T18:46:57-07:00</published><updated>2016-09-09T18:46:57-07:00</updated><id>/rackspace/hugo/development/2016/09/09/hugo-to-rackspace</id><content type="html" xml:base="/rackspace/hugo/development/2016/09/09/hugo-to-rackspace.html">&lt;p&gt;After reading Evan Browns post &lt;a href=&quot;http://evanbrown.io/post/hugo-on-the-go/&quot;&gt;Hugo on the go&lt;/a&gt; I was inspired to figure out how to do this exact same thing but as opposed to using AWS I wanted to use &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rackspace.com/cloud/files&quot;&gt;Rackspace Cloud FIles&lt;/a&gt; and more specfically Rackspace Static Website feature, because Rackspace Cloud Files is an inexpensive way to store and distribute objects, the Cloud Files static website feature coupled with the lightning-fast content delivery network (CDN) is a winning combination in terms of both performance and price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Creating a static website—a site that does not change for each request—with Cloud Files and the updated Control Panel is as easy as pointing and clicking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;to-set-up-a-static-webiste-using-the-rackspace-control-panel&quot;&gt;To set up a static webiste using the Rackspace Control Panel&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the Control Panel, you begin to set up your static website by creating a container.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Login to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://mycloud.rackspace.com&quot;&gt;Control Panel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In the Files section of the Control Panel, click &lt;strong&gt;Create Container&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fill in a name and a region for your static webite.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For &lt;strong&gt;Type&lt;/strong&gt;, select &lt;strong&gt;Static Website&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;Create Container&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In the Control Panel, click on your static website container, and then click the &lt;strong&gt;Upload Files&lt;/strong&gt; button.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In the File Upload dialog box, click &lt;strong&gt;Choose Files&lt;/strong&gt; and navigate to the folder with your content.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Select your content (you can select multiple files), and then click &lt;strong&gt;Open&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In the Control Panel, navigate to your container listing by clicking the &lt;strong&gt;Containers&lt;/strong&gt; link.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click the cog wheel next to your static website container, and then click &lt;strong&gt;View All Links&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the CDN URLs for your container are displayed. For HTML pages and pictures, use the HTTP link for your static website container.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;to-set-up-a-automated-deployments-using-travis-ci&quot;&gt;To set up a Automated Deployments using Travis CI&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once again my &lt;em&gt;.travis.yml&lt;/em&gt; file was very similar to Evan Browns except im using a few pieces to talk to rackspace’s cloud -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-bash highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;language: go                                                                                                                                  
go:
- 1.4
&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;install&lt;/span&gt;:
- go get github.com/spf13/hugo
script: hugo
before_deploy: &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;cd &lt;/span&gt;public
deploy:
  provider: cloudfiles
  username: RACKSPACE USERNAME
  api_key:
    secure: APIKEYFROMRACKSPACE
  region: REGION
  container: CONTAINERNAME
  skip_cleanup: &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;true
  &lt;/span&gt;on:
    repo: caseyCaseybecking/www_caseybecking_com_hugo
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Login to the Control Panel and goto &lt;strong&gt;Account Settings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Under &lt;strong&gt;Login Details&lt;/strong&gt; you will see &lt;strong&gt;API KEY&lt;/strong&gt; - Copy That&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Install the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/travis-ci/travis.rb&quot;&gt;Travis CLI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CD into your current hugo working directory&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Execute &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;travis setup cloudfiles&lt;/code&gt;
 &lt;em&gt;This will ask you a few questions for setup and create the *.travis.yml*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once this file is created you can push it to your repo (modification may be needed).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now withing Travis you should be able to view the repo within &lt;em&gt;My Repositories&lt;/em&gt; flip the switch so it is enabled and it should try to build.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="rackspace" /><category term="hugo" /><category term="development" /><summary type="html">After reading Evan Browns post Hugo on the go I was inspired to figure out how to do this exact same thing but as opposed to using AWS I wanted to use Rackspace Cloud FIles and more specfically Rackspace Static Website feature, because Rackspace Cloud Files is an inexpensive way to store and distribute objects, the Cloud Files static website feature coupled with the lightning-fast content delivery network (CDN) is a winning combination in terms of both performance and price.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">But I Run Magento</title><link href="/security/magento/2016/08/30/but-i-run-magento.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="But I Run Magento" /><published>2016-08-30T18:46:57-07:00</published><updated>2016-08-30T18:46:57-07:00</updated><id>/security/magento/2016/08/30/but-i-run-magento</id><content type="html" xml:base="/security/magento/2016/08/30/but-i-run-magento.html">&lt;p&gt;After working with many small and mid-sized retailers in 2015, there is one thing they all have in common the assumption that hackers won’t bother with them.   Actually it’s the reverse - criminals have figured out small companies are easier to penetrate, and go after them more frequently.  Why go for one big hack, of say eBay or Facebook,  when you can hack 5,000+ sites which NEVER take notice?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In spite of high-profile hacks such as against Apple, Cisco, or even the US Government, many online retailers still do not believe that they are at risk or have been a victim of undetected hacks by criminal groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www2.trustwave.com/rs/815-RFM-693/images/2015_TrustwaveGlobalSecurityReport.pdf&quot;&gt;2015 Trustwave Global Security Report&lt;/a&gt;, retail was the top industry compromised, making up 41% of the attacks investigated. And 65% of those attacks were against e-commerce sites, where hackers target servers and databases that host card data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s all put our &lt;em&gt;criminal hat&lt;/em&gt; on for a second and think about things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;PII (personally identifiable  information) is GOLD to a hacker.  It trades easy on the black market (dark web) and it’s value increases with more in-depth profiles such as username/pw, CC details, address, bill to, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Who has PII data readily available?  Online retailers!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cybercriminals are highly skilled technically and are also business people, who know how to make money. A recent CNN article said this: “According to one European intelligence service, there are 20-30 criminal gangs in the former Soviet Union that have hacking skills as good as most nations. There are many other groups with lesser skills. These criminals are nimble and inventive, and there are thriving cybercrime black markets where you can buy the latest hacking tools.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A recent Javelin Strategy &amp;amp; Research report found that financial institutions are doing a much better job than retailers when it comes to credit card security. Indeed, there are a number of online marketplaces and forums that solely exist to sell information gained by hackers, for example Rescator.la sells stolen credit and debit card information. In such places, customer databases from online stores are often the most expensive on the black market, because they contain correct, up-to-date and complete customer details, sometimes even with their credit card numbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Completeness is a very important factor for pricing on the black market. One customer record from an online store may generate a penny, while a thousand records can easily generate at least $10, or much more, depending on the records’ quality and completeness. For example spammers prefer to purchase e-mails from Internet retailers, simply because they will get a higher click-through rate, generating more revenue, as they can send targeted spam (by country, age, wealth, area of interests, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hackers are also interested in the valuable information on shoppers’ computers, so e-commerce web sites are often infected with malware (an exploit pack targeting and exploiting vulnerabilities in Adobe products or popular browsers). Such attacks often remain unnoticed as they are conducted overnight or at weekends when security team is away. Experienced hackers can go undetected over a long period. For example, French computer hardware retailer LaCie disclosed in April 2014 that its web site had been breached by a malware attack that went undetected for a year. Following the breach, the retailer recommended that buyers check their credit card statements for any fraudulent charges, and keep an eye on their credit reports in case of identity theft.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The big-name breaches that hit headlines leave many small and midsized e-business owners believing that they will not be attacked, assuming their customer databases are not big enough. This assumption is wrong because in the majority of cases hackers are not looking for customers and data from a specific web shop, they are just looking for commercially exploitable data. The more, the better. It’s much easier, faster and cheaper to hack 50 small e-boutiques than hacking one big one. Moreover, the outcome in terms of number of stolen customer records will be almost the same, probably even bigger. Imagine how much it costs to compromise Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Large e-commerce retailers also have much more administrative, financial and legal resources to organize forensics and post-incident investigation, so many hackers try to avoid them. Instead, they often target small retailers that have no capability to fight back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As only a small number of Black Hats have the necessary skills, time and resources to launch attacks against the biggest players in the e-commerce industry, hackers prefer to compromise a dozen small and medium online shops per day and get their money on the “every little bit helps” principle. Hacker groups use robots, hidden behind proxies, to crawl the Web in the 24/7/365 mode. They look for known vulnerabilities, outdated versions of web application software or just brute force default or weak passwords. One would be surprised how much information can be just found in Google. And if you have a crawling farm you can compromise thousands of web sites per hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Against this hacker onslaught, online retailers of all sizes need to employ an arsenal that is as flexible and up to date as the hackers’ tools. Retailers need to ensure that their hosting providers or data centers have stringent security procedures, that content management systems are up to date, third-party code is checked thoroughly before use and web sites are regularly audited for weaknesses through a combination of vulnerability scanning and penetration testing.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="security" /><category term="magento" /><summary type="html">After working with many small and mid-sized retailers in 2015, there is one thing they all have in common the assumption that hackers won’t bother with them. Actually it’s the reverse - criminals have figured out small companies are easier to penetrate, and go after them more frequently. Why go for one big hack, of say eBay or Facebook, when you can hack 5,000+ sites which NEVER take notice?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">You’ve been hacked!  What to do to save your business.</title><link href="/security/magento/2016/08/30/youve-been-hacked.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="You’ve been hacked!  What to do to save your business." /><published>2016-08-30T18:46:57-07:00</published><updated>2016-08-30T18:46:57-07:00</updated><id>/security/magento/2016/08/30/youve-been-hacked</id><content type="html" xml:base="/security/magento/2016/08/30/youve-been-hacked.html">&lt;p&gt;There’s no denying that E-commerce has grown at an enormous rate in the last decade.  For many companies, eCommerce has quickly become the fastest growing channel; if not the largest channel of sales.    Yet sadly, with growth, come those who’d also like to profit from the hundreds of thousands of unprotected sites, ripe with personal data and payment details.   Successful ecommerce platforms, such as Magento with 200,000+ installs, makes for a ripe target for the savvy hacker.   Daily attempts to intrude payment processes, gain access to data bases, etc. allows them to resell personal data and/or take a cut of the transaction, which can certainly provide a luxurious living for hackers.
These malicious elements try to penetrate e-commerce sites to get to merchant accounts.  More often than not, it’s a door or window that’s left open; where a company has failed to install a security update, used soft usernames, or simply bad programming.   Once successful, the hacker downloads your customer’s personal information. (Username, Address, Payment details, etc).   eCommerce hackers are mostly after CC data, user data, and access to payment gateway details so they can shave pennies/dollars off of orders without the company knowing.   In 80% of the cases we’ve seen, these compromised sites aren’t aware of the breach for over a year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In many cases, there are signs that your e-commerce site has been breached.
They are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If your payment gateway uses Address Verification System (AVS) and Card Security Codes, where the transaction does not contain any AVS or CVV2/CVC2 requests.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Site speed and page load performance during checkout. (common when your checkout is now being asked to make an add’l call, per the hacker’s design.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If the transaction does not include any Customer Identification Information.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If there are several transactions within a really short period on your magneto platform or any other ecommerce platform you operate on.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Repeat User ID access to the database at odd hours.  (often it’s a valid username &amp;amp; password)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Offset the balances when reconciling transactions at the end of the month.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Suspicious multiple transactions from the same IP (Internet Protocol) address&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve have experienced any of these signs, simply take these five steps to assist in the recovery of your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take your website offline
You should tentatively shut the site down while it is being assessed and fixed.  Stop the bleeding!  For example, adding a text file named “maintenance.flag” to the web root of a Magento-based site will put the site into maintenance mode and display a 503 service unavailable message to site visitors.
(We strongly recommend customizing the 503 message, offering customers a phone number to call if they have questions about an order or even posting a discount code for free shipping when the site comes back up.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2 . Change all passwords and control access going forward
Despite warnings, soft passwords are still commonplace and result in site hacks.   Take the time to review all user accounts, access levels, permissions, etc. and close off any potential vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Scan your local computers for viruses and malware
You will need to scan your entire environment and touch points to 3rd party solutions with an anti-virus software to ensure the are not infected with malware, Trojan, spyware, etc. Be sure your anti-virus software is up-to-date before using it to scan your computer.
If you’re running Magento code, you’re in luck, you can conduct a free scan of your code base at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sekursite.com/site-scan/&quot;&gt;https://www.sekursite.com/site-scan/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Clean up the site
With the help of a security minded developer, systems integrator, or consultancy, you might be able to discover the malicious code affecting your site.   Delete all code found and refresh with a clean installation from a backup and manually check all plugin folders.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Notify your ecommerce software provider.
Yes, getting hacked can be embarrassing, painful, and emotional.  Yet, now is your chance to spread the word and help others.   If you remain silent, software vendors will go on believing that their code bases have “never been hacked” and other industry peers using that code base will certainly fall victim to the same scan.   Once successful many hackers will simply ‘rinse &amp;amp; repeat’, deploying their code to other sites on the same platform by exploiting the same holes found on your site.   Contact your software provider pronto!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you feel your site has been compromised or you’d like to test your site’s security, don’t hesitate to take a free scan today. Click &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sekursite.com/site-scan/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; Let them find the holes in your site before someone else does.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="security" /><category term="magento" /><summary type="html">There’s no denying that E-commerce has grown at an enormous rate in the last decade. For many companies, eCommerce has quickly become the fastest growing channel; if not the largest channel of sales. Yet sadly, with growth, come those who’d also like to profit from the hundreds of thousands of unprotected sites, ripe with personal data and payment details. Successful ecommerce platforms, such as Magento with 200,000+ installs, makes for a ripe target for the savvy hacker. Daily attempts to intrude payment processes, gain access to data bases, etc. allows them to resell personal data and/or take a cut of the transaction, which can certainly provide a luxurious living for hackers. These malicious elements try to penetrate e-commerce sites to get to merchant accounts. More often than not, it’s a door or window that’s left open; where a company has failed to install a security update, used soft usernames, or simply bad programming. Once successful, the hacker downloads your customer’s personal information. (Username, Address, Payment details, etc). eCommerce hackers are mostly after CC data, user data, and access to payment gateway details so they can shave pennies/dollars off of orders without the company knowing. In 80% of the cases we’ve seen, these compromised sites aren’t aware of the breach for over a year.</summary></entry></feed>